由路易斯·莱恩为您带来星球日报新闻
Daily Planet News with Lois Lane.
今日头条：海中的正义
Today's top story: justice by sea.
看来黑蝠鲼是今日的收获
Looks like Black Manta is the catch of the day.
陆上的正义
Justice by land.
噢，这只企鹅看来需要一个冰袋了
Oh. This Penguin is going to need an ice pack.
哈哈. - 啊！
Ha-ha. - Aah!
太空的正义
Justice in space.
我打赌塞尼斯托现在已经意识到自己处境危机
I bet Sinestro is now aware of the gravity of his situation.
我真希望这些超级反派们都买过保险，因为他们确实挺需要的
I hope supervillains have health insurance
because it looks like they're gonna need it.
自从数月之前正义联盟组建以来，他们至今没有输过一场
Since the Justice League's formation months ago, they have yet to lose a battle.
从今往后，如果你想看任何超级反派的镜头...
From now on, if you wanna see any supervillain footage...
你就得去看看世界最佳滑稽节目
you'll have to watch The World's Most Ridiculous and Embarrassing Videos.
回到日常报道
Back to the actual news.
军方的核量子反应堆今日开始运行
The Army's prototype nuketron reactor began operating today.
这座实验发电厂将会成为比联合发电更多的能量.
This experimental power plant will generate more energy than the combined-
够了
Enough of that.
抛开她糟糕的语法和烂透的报道不谈...
Despite her bad grammar and terrible reporting...
「无畏的」路易斯·莱恩是对的啊
the intrepid Lois Lane is correct.
正义联盟让我们失业了
The Justice League is putting us out of business.
你描绘的情景比马里亚纳海沟底还黑暗啊，卢瑟
You paint a picture as black as the bottom
of the Mariana Trench, Luthor.
显然事情并没有那么糟糕
Surely things can't be that bad.
不，蝠鲼，卢瑟是对的
No, Manta, Luthor is right.
我们的未来十分悲观并且将会失败重重
Our glass is half empty and the full half is full of failure.
过去，我们每人和英雄单打独斗时还有点机会赢
In the past, each of us fighting a lone hero had some chance of winning.
但现在，对抗他们全部？
But now, against all of them?
我跟你说...
I say to you...
如果世界上的超级罪犯想要生存下去...
that if the supercriminals of the world want to survive...
我们必须要团结起来形成 非正义的联盟，
we too must band together and form, not a league of justice...
成立一个军团，
but a legion.
毁灭军团
A Legion of Doom.
噢，真恶心
Ah, sheesh.
他们上钩了
They went for it.
一切按我的计划进行
Everything is going according to my plan.
你的计划，卢瑟？
Your plan, Luthor?
我允许你加入我的计划是因为这能助我的目的一臂之力
I'm allowing your participation in my plan because it serves my purpose.
召集他们
Summon them.
把这世上最卑鄙无耻的恶棍们都召集到这里...
Summon the world's vilest villains here...
到这毁灭大厅...
to this, this Hall of Doom...
开始我征服地球的计划
to begin my conquest of the Earth.
最终，正义联盟败给了达克赛德
And so the Justice League falls to Darkseid.
Booyah!
投降吧，笨蛋
Surrender now, Dork-sew.
你可挡不住我的力量，孩子
You are no match for my power, child.
「抬」头
Heads up.
糊你熊脸
In your face.
世界最强钢骨！嗷！
World's best cyborg! Ow!
跟着我一起摇摆
I put the boogie in the berg
钢骨
The Cyborg
你救了我的命，钢骨.
You saved my life, Cyborg.
蝙蝠侠的命  - 嗯哼
Batman's life. - Mm-hm.
令人惊叹，我们应该多出去玩玩. - 喔！
Impressive. We should hang out more.  - Whoo!
当然，蝙蝠侠，那真是太棒了
Sure, Batman. That would be great.
我在蝙蝠洞里有个台球桌，而且...
I've got a pool table back at the Batcave and--
等等，啥？台球？台球听起来棒极了
Wait, what? Pools? Pools sound great.
我挺喜欢玩台球的...呃，哈？
I'd just totally love to play pool with... Uh, huh?
噢，我去，刚刚那是个梦？
Oh, dang, it was a dream?
噢，不，不，不.我睡过头了
Oh, no, no, no. I overslept.
我要迟到了
I'm gonna be late.
我会议要迟到了
I'm gonna be late for the meeting.
又一次
Again.
该死的缆线
Stupid cord.
你迟到了，钢骨
You're late, Cyborg.
额，嗨，大家好啊
Uh, hi, everybody.
维克，难道你体内没有内置一个原子钟吗？
Vic, don't you have like an atomic clock built into you?
抱歉...嘿嘿...我只是...
Sorry about-- Heh-heh. I ju--
我晚起是因为我忙一个秘密项目，可以...
I was up late working on a secret project, which--
不要介意了，年轻的钢骨，你还没来的时候我们就开始了
Think nothing of it, young Cyborg. We started without you.
等了好几百万年后，我感觉大概有五百万年
After waiting a million years, which feels like 5 million years to me.
超级速度带来的坏处
The downside of super-speed.
放松，闪电侠，吃个甜甜圈吧
Relax，Flash.Have a doughnut
哦，天哪
Oh, boy.
嘿，等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
只剩一个甜甜圈了，妈妈总是教育我要有礼貌
There's only one. Mom raised me to have manners.
这个甜甜圈应该给你，神奇女侠
That doughnut should go to you,Wonder Woman.
好吧，你真是有绅士风度，闪电侠，但是...
Well, that's very chivalrous, Flash, but--
噗，他？绅士风度？你在开玩笑？
Pfft. Him? Chivalrous? Are you kidding?
就因为给了你一个甜甜圈？
Offering you a doughnut?
哇哦！ - 公主殿下应该拥有一个王座
Whoa! - A princess should have a throne.
哈尔，我是神奇女侠，我可不需要什么特殊待遇
Hal, I'm Wonder Woman,I certainly don't require special
来咯.世界各地的美味佳肴
There. Delicacies from around the world.
总有食物适合公主的口味
Food fit for the palate of a princess.
好了，都坐下，你们俩
Okay, sit down, both of you.
坐下
Sit.
如你们所知，今天是选举日
As you know, it's election day.
我们要选出一位新的英雄来领导正义联盟
We'll be voting for a new hero to lead the Justice League.
请吧，各位，用心投票
Please, everyone, vote with your heart.
我有异议，钢铁之躯
I beg to differ, Man of Steel.
要知道为做出艰难决定的候选人投票
You see Vote for the candidate who makes hard decisions...
是基于冰冷的数据和可靠的自觉
based on cold data and infallible instincts.
现在，我建议我们用投票选举
Now, I suggest we take that vote.
我投给神奇女侠一票 - 我可连竞选都没参加
I vote for Wonder Woman. - I'm not even running.
她是候选人的话我也给她一票，两票
She's a write-in and I'm voting for her.Twice.
我投票给超人，这位实际参选了的人
My vote goes to Superman,who is actually running.
我投票给黑暗骑士
My vote goes to the Dark Knight.
无意冒犯啦，超人 - 哦，没事没事
No offense, Superman.- Oh, none taken.
嗯.看来是平局
Hmm. Looks like a tie...
毕竟我和超人毫无疑都会投票给自己的
since Superman and I undoubtedly voted for ourselves.
我可从来都没想过
That never even occurred to me.
我投你一票
I voted for you.
所以赢家是 蝙蝠侠
And the winner is Batman.
太好了，黑暗骑士.来击个掌
All right, Dark Knight. Up high.
恭喜，蝙蝠侠
Congratulations, Batman.
系统里投你票的人包括我保证都绝对相信
The people have spoken and my absolute faith in the system assures me...
你是一个正确的领导者
that you are clearly the correct leader.
危险警报
The trouble alert.
大都会第一国家银行发生抢劫案
A robbery at Metropolis First National Bank.
有什么指令，主管？
What's the word, chief?
闪电侠，指令就是「出发」
The word, Flash, is "go."
不许动
Freeze!
站在那不要动，小丑
Hold it right there, Joker.
我不是小丑，我是魔术师
I'm not the Joker. I'm the Trickster.
完全不一样好吗
Totally different.
小丑会用一罐子蛇来攻击吗
Would the Joker attack with a can of snakes?
额.会吧，他很可能真会这么做 - 很像他的作风
Yeah. Yeah. He probably would.- Sounds like him.
哇哦！- 啊！
Whoa!- Aah!
哈？ - 嘿，小丑把我们的车炸飞了
Huh? - Hey, the Joker just blew up our car.
不，那甚至都不算一个笑话
No. That's not even a joke.
这是一个魔术，就像这个魔术鞋一样，小丑可没有魔术鞋
It's a trick. Like trick shoes.
The Joker doesn't have trick shoes.
我是魔术师，魔~术~师~
I'm the Trickster. The Trickster.
啊，我们的老朋友，魔术师
Ah. Our old friend, the Trickster.
终于，有认识我的了
Finally. He gets me.
我知道他不是我们的朋友，我只是在讽刺
I know he isn't really our friend. I was being ironic.
现在是我的下一个魔术：消失魔法
And now for my next trick: a disappearing act.
我可不是这货魔术的粉丝
I'm not a fan of this guy's tricks.
那边
There.
正义联盟，分散开找他
Justice League, split up and find him.
并小心他那些陈旧的魔术
And watch out for his corny tricks.
你现在无处可逃了，魔术师
No escape for you now, Trickster.
我会搞定他的，闪电侠
I got this, Flash.
不，是我会搞定
No, I got this.
书中最古老的魔法
The oldest trick in the book.
等着看神奇女侠听到你被香蕉绊倒了是什么反应吧.啊！
Wait till Wonder Woman hears that you fell for a banana. Unh!
没有他的踪迹
No sign of him.
你躲不过我的透视眼的，魔术师
You can't hide from my x-ray vision, Trickster.
我找到他了
I found him.
你到此为止了，魔术师
End of the line for you, Trickster.
嗯？
Huh?
我们很快就会把你从这个下水道里找出来的，魔术师
We'll flush you out of this sewer soon enough, Trickster.
我的感应器在这条隧道检测到动静
My sensors are picking up movement in this tunnel.
有东西在那里
There's something down there.
哇哦
Whoa!
看来我的蝙蝠牙线该派上用场了
Looks like a job for my Bat-dental floss.
你已经没有伎俩了，魔术师
You've gimmicked your last gimmick, Trickster.
你的诡计就是累赘
Your gags are a drag.
你已经无计可施了
You're bag of tricks just ran out.
你的魔术将给你带来一场
Your tricks just treated you to a trip...
直达黑门监狱的旅途
Right to Blackgate Prison.
正义联盟的又一场胜利，来击个掌
Another win for the Justice League. High five.
什么五个？ - 呃
Five what? - Ugh.
投降吧，魔术师
Come quietly, Trickster.
你们要么让我走.
You either let me go...
要么我就要释放我手上的气体
or we're gonna have a smelly situation on our hands.
我来处理
I got this.
喔
Ooh!
现在该解决这个 - 钢骨，等等
And now to dispose of it.- Cyborg, wait.
嗯？
Huh?
啊-哦
Uh-oh.
我做到了，booyah~
I did it. Booyah!
恶...这是啥味儿？
Ew! What's that smell?
喔，真难闻 - 喔，这真糟糕
Oh, that's nasty. - Oh, that's bad.
那是什么？
What is that?
看上去钢骨要挨蝙蝠好一顿说了
Looks like Cyborg's about to get a Bat lecture.
幸好我不是他
Glad I'm not in his shoes.
我刚才就是想告诉你这个，钢骨
I was trying to tell you, Cyborg.
那是个臭气弹
That was a stink bomb.
现在整个街道都是恶臭
Now this whole section of the city stinks.
更别提你们了，咻...
Not to mention you guys. Phew.
嘿嘿，看来我笑到了最后啊，正义联盟
Heh-heh. Looks like I got the last laugh, Justice League.
呃
Ew.
呃，对不起？
Uh, Oops?
欢迎来到毁灭军团
Welcome to the Legion of Doom.
毁灭障碍训练场
Obstacle Course of Doom.
打败正义联盟不是小事，因此我们军团只要
Defeating the Justice League is no small
matter so our legion must be comprised...
选拔出技巧最熟练的恶棍
of only the most skilled of scoundrels.
你们的任务：在训练场上活下来，碾碎你们的竞争者
Your task: survive the course, crush your competition...
向军团证明你的邪恶
validate your villainy for the legion.
这里没有规则
There are no rules!
什么？等一下
What? Wait a minute.
好吧，有一条规则，军团成员必须参加总部
Okay, there is one rule. Club members have to be able to attend...
各项会议和社交事宜
meetings and social events inside our headquarters...
我看有的人估计连门都不能进来
and I see someone here who won't even fit through the door.
抱歉，巨化女
Sorry, Giganta.
规则就是规则
Rules are rules.
好了，闲话少说，让我们马上开始吧
All right, now without further ado,
I'd like to get things started.
他们出发了
And they're off.
第一关是弹射...
This first section should put a little spring in their step.
和坠落，哈哈
And a little fall. Ha-ha-ha.
豹女一马当先
Here comes Cheetah.
看来猫也不总是能够优雅落地嘛
Looks like cats don't always land on their feet after all.
猩猩格鲁德荡过了机械鳄鱼
Gorilla Grodd swings past the Robe-gators.
但接下来这关会让他困在香蕉中
But this next section is going to drive him bananas.
哦，人蝠都快被打成人蚊了，哈哈哈，人蚊
Ooh. Man-Bat swatted like a man-gnat. Ha-ha-ha. Man-gnat.
我们来到了致命甜甜圈
We're coming up to the Deadly Doughnuts.
豹女掉下去了
And Cheetah gets dunked.
小丑来得正好刚好赶上公交
Joker's right on time to catch the bus.
这关是一头怪兽，
Ha-ha-ha. This course is a monster...
看来企鹅人的全力也就这样了
and it looks like it just got the best of Penguin.
这真是太逗了
That was priceless.
太棒了，太棒了
Too good. Too good.
比赛结束了
This contest is over.
等等，少了个选手
Wait a minute. There's one competitor missing.
U额，这货是谁来着？
h, who is this guy again?
终结者-丧钟
Deathstroke the Terminator.
-老牛逼了 -也许他才该来当老大
- Most impressive.
-Maybe he should be the leader.
谢谢您了
Thank you.
Huh?
我们赢啦
We made it.
不幸的是，我们只有六个停车位...
Unfortunately, we only have six parking spots...
所以，拜拜咯
so goodbye.
恭喜，你们入伙了
Congratulations. You're in.
欢迎我们的新同伴
And welcome to all our new members.
收起你那一套吧，莱秃
Keep your kudos, Lex.
我们只是想犯点罪而已
What we want is crime.
那就去犯吧，豹女
And so you shall have it, Cheetah.
这个政府秘密设施被称为52区
This is a covert government facility known as Area 52.
额，你是说51区？
Don't you mean Area 51?
旧的51区已经关了
The old Area 51 was shut down.
这是新52
This is the new 52.
这个顶级机密的政府基地
It is a top secret government base...
藏满了高级实验武器以及没收的外星科技
full of advanced experimental weaponry
and confiscated alien technology.
他们不想这些东西落入坏人之手
They don't want any of it
falling into the wrong hands.
当然这里的坏人，嘿嘿，指的就是我们
And by the wrong hands, heh-heh，they mean our hands.
正是如此
Quite so.
毁灭军团，邪恶全开吧
Legion of Doom, prepare for evil.
耶
Yeah.
啊！哦！
Aah! Ooh!
钢骨的功能停止运转了吗？
Have Cyborg's functions terminated?
没有，电子机器人，我没死
No, (By-bot, I'm not dead.
我想给正义大厅升下级，但是有点分心了
I was working on some new upgrades
for the hall, but I'm a little distracted.
钢骨有什么故障吗
What is Cyborg's malfunction?
额，我今天搞了个又大又臭的麻烦出来，
Well, I kind of made a big, stinky mess today.
我不觉得其他人现在想看见我
I'm not sure the others want me around right now.
钢骨把电子机器人设计成进行清洁和做家务
Cyborg designed Cy-bot to clean and perform chores.
电子机器人会清理好钢骨又大又臭的麻烦的
Cy-bot will clean Cyborg's big, stinky mess.
你说得对，电子机器人，
You're right, Cy-bot.
我需要自己清理我的麻烦
I need to clean up my own messes.
救命
Help.
嘿，伙计们，那个我想道歉...哇？！
Hey, guys, I just wanted to apolog...Wha--
哇哦
Whoa.
你们换新制服了
You guys got new outfits!
超人，你把内裤穿在里面了？
Superman, you're wearing your underwear on the inside?
不错的选择
Nice choice.
还有，蝙蝠侠，黑暗骑士的闪亮新战甲
And, Batman, shiny new armor for the Dark Knight.
神奇女侠，还是一如既往的爱国，但是更低调了
Wonder Woman, patriotic as always, but more understated.
闪电侠和哈尔...额...你们俩没变化啊
Flash and Hal, well...You haven't changed a bit.
我的制服完美无暇
My costume is an indestructible construct.
为何要破坏完美的结构
And why mess with perfection?
我说得对吧，公主殿下？
Am I right, princess?
噗.你带着那拖累你的珠宝才能坚不可摧吧
Pfft. You'd better be indestructible
with that jewelry slowing you down.
你可比不上这完美突显出「世上最快的人」的制服
You can't beat a costume that screams "fastest man alive."
比世上其他人都快的人，你怎么还不闪到一边去？
So why don't you brush off, faster than any man alive?
干什...？嘿. - 嘿
- What the--? Hey. -Heh.
哇哦，哇哦，我不明白，到底发生了什么
Whoa, whoa, I don't understand. What's going on here?
我们的旧制服沾上了永久的恶臭而毁了
Our former costumes were ruined with a permanent stench.
它有损我们作为犯罪斗士的效率
It compromised our effectiveness as crime-fighters.
对，因为我你们的旧制服才都会变臭的
Right, because it's my fault your old ones got all stinky.
没有的事
Nonsense.
我们都需要改变
We all needed a change.
要不我们也给你来点新东西？
Why don't we come up with something new for you too?
-我们不能，神奇女侠 -为什么？
- We can't, Wonder Woman. -Why?
钢骨不穿衣服的啊
Cyborg doesn't wear clothes.
-有警报 - 正义联盟，这里是莱恩将军
- The trouble alert.- Justice League, this is General Lane.
52区，一个顶级机密的政府机构指挥官
commanding officer of Area 52,
a top secret government installation.
我们正遭到未知人员的攻击
We are under attack from person or persons unknown.
但是很有可能是外星人
But it's probably alien.
您说的好像是什么脏东西一样，将军
You say that like it's a bad thing, general.
赶紧过来并采取...
Just get over here and take a...
快走吧，我光站这感觉自己开始变老了
Let's go. I can feel myself
growing older just standing here.
别着急，闪电侠
Not so fast, Flash.
蝙蝠侠是我们正式选举的领导人，
Batman is the duly-elected leader.
要由他来决定
This is his call.
准备起飞标枪号
Prepare the Javelin for launch.
打起精神，伙计们，我们进入了52区上空
Look alive, team, we've entered Area 52 airspace.
噢，一个政府绝密基地，藏满了各种绝密科技，
Ooh. A top secret government compound
loaded with top secret technology...
坐落于一个绝密的位置
and located in a top secret location.
你是怎么找到它的？
How'd you even know where to find it?
-我是...-...蝙蝠侠！
-I'm...  -Batman.
对吧，我懂的
Right? Gotcha.
Hmm.
这很安静
It's quiet.
太安静了
Too quiet.
除了这特雷门的电子音乐
Except for the theremin music.
钢骨，能把它关了吗?
Cyborg, would please stop it?
不好意思，我只是有点小紧...卡车！
Sorry, I was just having a little bit a...Truck!
欢迎你们来被打败，正义联盟
Welcome to your defeat, Justice League.
败在毁灭军团的手里
Defeat at the hands of the Legion of Doom.
版权与商标已注册
Copyright and trademark.
呃，毁灭军团?
Ah! Legion of Doom?
-石化的潘多拉 - 反派们联手了?
- Petrified Pandora.
-Villains working together?
-我可没想到会这样 - 我想到了
- I did not see that coming. -I did.
干掉他们
Destroy them.
正义联盟，行动！
Justice League, move out.
你们听到了队长的话了，行动吧
You heard our captain. Let's move.
超人，你的联盟比不过...
Superman, your league is no match...
毁灭军团
for the Legion of Doom!
你该加入个差劲枪法军团什么的
You should've joined the Legion of Bad Marksmanship.
毁灭军团会取你项上人头
The Legion of Doom will have your heads.
长尾巴的，你输了
Tails. You lose.
站住，你这个烦躁轻浮的小子
Hold still, you fidgety flibbertigibbet.
烦躁轻浮小子?烦躁轻浮是个啥?
Flibbertigibbet? What's a flibbertigibbet?
噢
Ooh!
哦，不
Oh, no.
你是躲不掉的，格鲁德
It's no use trying to hide from me, Grodd.
谁躲了，
Who's hiding?
我只是在熟悉我的新座驾
I'm just getting a feel for my new ride.
嘿，那下有点痛
Hey, I felt that.
学校开始授课了，年轻人
School's in session, youngster.
好啊，这是我的作业
Well, here's my homework.
噢
Ooh!
下课
Class dismissed.
嘿，塞尼斯托
Hey, Sinestro.
迎接你最可怕的噩梦吧
Here comes your worst nightmare.
我最可怕的噩梦是穿着内裤在公众场合演讲
My worst nightmare involves public speaking in my underwear.
你还差得远呢
You're not even close.
欢迎乘坐干草机特快列车
All aboard the Haymaker Express.
哈哈，票已检
Ha-ha. Ticket punched.
尝尝这个，你个寄生弹球
Take this, you parasitic pinball.
没打中，差一点，
Missed me. Nice try.
下次好运吧
Better luck next time.
全中，输家
Full tilt, loser.
现在轮到你这个半人类
Now to finish off the half-man.
机器人，这就是你的极限了吗?
So, Robot Man, is that all you can do?
当真正的人类在干正事时呆在一边什么都不做?
Sit there while the real men do the work?
该死的电梯，
Stupid elevator.
快啊，打开，打开
Come on. Open. Open.
不可能，我都把这玩意开到11级了
Impossible. I have this thing turned up to 11.
丢掉你那没用的地球科技吧，卢瑟
Forget your worthless Earth technology, Luthor.
走这个轰爆音通道
Enter this boom tube.
这是一个由父盒控制的跨维度通道
It is an inter-dimensional gateway controlled by this Father Box.
另一个达克赛德的礼物
Yet another gift of Darkseid.
为什么你在毁灭大厅的时候不直接用爆音通道把我们送过来
Why didn't you just boom tube us here from the Hall of Doom?
我暂时还不想让你们军团的人知道我的存在
It is not my will that your legion knows of me, yet.
进来，你在浪费时间
Come. You are wasting time.
要是我们不是飞过来的话还可以省一大把时间呢
Could've saved a lot of time if we hadn't flown here.
从屠杀沼泽飞过来花了三小时...，
It was a three-hour flight from Slaughter Swamp...
而且黑蝠鲼的飞船闻起来就像死鱼一样
and Manta's ship smells like a wharf.
了不起的科技，有了这个我就可以...
Impressive technology. With these tubes, I could take over the--
你就可以利用我给你的工具征服这个可怜的世界
You will take over this pitiful world with the tools I give you.
我很乐意接受你的援助，暂时
I am happy to accept your aid. For now.
你说啥
What was that?
噢，我说我很乐意把创可贴贴牛身上...
Oh, I said I like to put Band-Aids on cows.
地下13层，硬件，内衣，
Sub level 13. Hardware. Underwear.
禁止的外星科技
Forbidden alien technology.
站着别动你这外星怪物
Hold it right there, you alien weirdo.
我就知道，外星人想要统治这个星球
I knew it. Aliens trying to take over the planet.
对不住了，有我萨姆·莱恩将军在就没戏
Well, sorry, pal, not on General Sam Lane's watch.
多么离奇有趣
How quaint.
修正，硬件，内衣，
Correction. Hardware. Underwear.
不省人事的偏执狂将军
Unconscious paranoid generals.
密封罐就那边，
The cylinder is right over there.
去吧
Go.
难以置信
Incredible.
啊，有人记下来车牌号了吗
Unh.Did somebody get the license number?
你的宇宙宝石搞不定吗，哈尔？
Oh, is your space jewelry not cutting it,Hal?
来，我教你要怎么做
Here, let me show you how to get your hands dirty.
啊? 啊?
Huh? Huh?
噢，不
Oh, no!
好了，这样就应该差不...
There. That ought to take the chill out--
我要把你们俩变成勇者和冷电侠
You two are about to become the brave and the cold.
这工作得需要一些无聊的东西来才能搞定
This jobs calls for something dull and blunt.
嘿
Hey
哈哈哈 - 啊？
Ha-ha-ha. Huh?
你只会用蝙蝠镖吗，蝙蝠侠?
Are Batarangs all you've got, Batman?
你要知道，黑蝠鲼，我是练过秘密武术的
You should know, Black Manta, that I'm
trained in the secret skills of martial arts.
你的激光和铠甲敌不过这古老的震动掌
Your lasers and armor are no match
for the ancient vibrating palm technique.
投降吧
Surrender now.
我的答案是不，蠢货
Here's your answer, fool.
哦不，我的电量
Oh, no, my battery.
有猫
Cat.
你这蠢猫，我看不见路了
You frustrating feline, I can't see!
毁灭军团，任务完成了，
Legion of Doom, mission accomplished.
让我们胜利撤退吧
Let us make our victorious retreat.
莱秃拿到了什么?
What's Lex got there?
肯定不妙
Nothing good.
哦，不，别跑
Oh, no, you don't.
还想在上一课吗，机器小子
Back for another lesson, Robot Boy?
来个突击测验吧
Here's a pop quiz.
你输了
You failed.
又一次，要由我给猪队友们来收拾烂摊子
Once again, it's up to me to clean up after lesser people's messes.
他们要逃走了
They're getting away.
有我在就没人能偷走政府的财产
Nobody steals government property while I'm around.
超人，你没事吧
Superman, you okay?
那推进器还真是够有劲的
Those afterburners really pack a punch.
反派们合作？
Villains working together?
这只是个时间问题
It was only a matter of time.
但是我们可是教训了他们一顿，
Ah, but we kicked their butts.
来击掌
Up high.
我们得解决一下击掌问题
We gotta work on that.
你们让他们逃走了
You let them get away.
别拿你军队的那套来唬人，将军
Don't get your Army-issued undies in a bunch, admiral.
他们只是拿了一罐子巨型汽水什么的
The only thing they got was a giant can of soda or something.
那是个外星人
It was an alien.
一个来自外太空的危险怪物
A dangerous monster from space.
而你们因为自己的无能让他从手指缝中溜走了
And you let it slip through your fingers because of your incompetence.
如果只是无能的话就好了
If it was incompetence.
我怎么知道你们外星人不是一伙的
How do I know all you aliens
aren't in cahoots?
嘿，超人不是外星人
Hey, Superman isn't an alien.
他是...额...好吧我想他的确是
He's a-- Oh, yeah, I guess he kind of is.
等一下，闪电侠
Wait a minute, Flash.
真正的问题是，你为什么囚禁外星人?
The real question is, why are you incarcerating aliens?
呃，那个....
Ugh. Well...
我不是该被审讯的人，超人
I'm not the one being questioned here,Superman.
现在如果你不介意，我还有个政府财产要去找
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've got government property to locate.
我们政府一定没有在囚禁外星人吧
Surely our government isn't arresting extraterrestrials.
根据我对他行为的分析
Based on my analysis of his behavior...
莱恩将军做的事大大地超出了他的权限
more likely that General Lane is greatly exceeding his authority.
怎么拉长着一张脸，钢骨
Why the long face, Cyborg?
你独自一人对抗了如此强大的对手，干得不错
You held your own against a formidable opponent. Good job.
不错？他们逃走了
Good job? They got away.
如果不是因为我，我们本可以阻止他们的
If it wasn't for me, we could have stopped them.
你还是这个团队里最年轻以及最伟大的成员
You're still the youngest and greenest member of this team.
放轻松
Cut yourself some slack.
别对自己太苛刻了，小子，你做得不错
Yeah, don't be so hard on yourself, kid.You did fine.
这是我们头一次面对一整个具有超能力的团队
Look, this is the first time we've met a completely superpowered team.
这太出人意料，肯定会有很多成长的烦恼
It was a total surprise. There were bound to be some growing pains.
问题是，我们下次相遇会怎么样？
The question is, what happens next time we meet?
该死的震动掌
Stupid vibrating palm.
被一个废柴军团缠住
Stuck with a Legion of Losers.
是啊，你们都没人支援我的
Yeah, none of you had my back.
我一直是一人
I was all alone.
那也总比跟格鲁德一起困在飞碟里好
Better alone than stuck in a saucer
with Grodd.
这次失败是个耻辱
That was a humiliating defeat.
-干得漂亮，各位. -  啊?
- Excellent work, everyone. - Huh?
你疯了吗，莱克斯，我们好不容易才逃出来已经很幸运了
Are you nuts, Lex? We were lucky to make it out of there in one piece.
对啊，你说我们要毁掉正义联盟
Yeah, you said we'd destroy the Justice League.
你对我们作为一个团队的能力的估计
Your estimate of our effectiveness as a team...
还有很多值得商权，卢瑟
...left much to be desired, Luthor.
听听你们说的
Listen to you all.
你们因为在一场公平对抗中没打败正义联盟而失望？
You're disappointed that you didn't beat
the Justice League in a fair fight?
超级恶棍的哪一方面你们没有理解？
What part of supervillain do you not comprehend?
我的科鲁加朋友说的没错
My Korugarian friend is correct.
我们突袭52区的目的是给我们弄个秘密武器，
The whole point of our raid on Area 52 was to give us a secret weapon...
让胜利天平倒向我们
to tip the scales in our favor.
一张王牌
A game-changer.
就是它了
Here it is.
Hmm?
冷静下来，我的朋友，你现在安全了
Calm yourself, friend. You're safe now.
我，莱克斯·卢瑟，解放你
I, Lex Luthor, release you.
Yipe!
你看见了我的自由斗士团队是怎么拼死战斗
You saw how my band of freedom fighters battled to rescue you...
把你从那卑鄙的正义联盟手中救出来的...
from the clutches of the dastardly Justice League...
那群我们世界的残酷暴君
the horrible oppressors of our world.
我们都是一伙的
We're all on your side.
是的，别害怕
It's true. Don't be afraid.
我们毁灭军团反抗军解放了你
We rebels in the Legion of Doom freed you.
告诉他们你的名字
Tell them your name.
尚恩·琼兹...
J'onn J'onzz.
我叫尚恩·琼兹，来自你们称为火星的星球
I am J'onn J'onzz of the planet you call Mars.
感谢你拯救了我
Thank you for freeing me.
很好，那这小小的太空蜥蜴怎么帮助我们呢
Swell. How is this little space lizard
supposed to help us, Luthor, huh?
给他们看看你的能力，我的朋友
Show them what you can do, my friend.
棒极了
Fantastic.
好，那你是否愿意加入我们的正义革命推翻正义联盟的暴政呢
Now, will you join our righteous revolution
against the tyranny of the Justice League?
但是你们这名字，毁灭军团...
But your name, Legion of Doom...
是指的正义联盟的毁灭
As in doom for the Justice League.
一个让他们闻风丧胆的名字
A name to strike fear into their wicked hearts.
-对对，是这个意思 -你说的没错
- Yeah, yeah, that's exactly what it meant.
-You are correct. Yes.
那些关押我的人应该受到惩罚
Those who held me captive should be punished.
-太好啦 -说得对
- Outstanding. -All right!
据观测：钢骨和正义联盟呆在一起的时间越来越少了...
Observation: Cyborg is spending less time with the Justice League...
而升级正义大厅却花费了越来越多的时间
and more time performing upgrades to the Hall of Justice.
提问：为什么呢
Query: Why?
没用的
It's no use.
我的兴趣爱好都没法让我静下心来，我需要一些建议
Not even my hobby can clear my mind. I need some advice.
救命
Help.
我这辈子就想当个英雄，
I've wanted to be a hero my whole life...
而加入正义联盟使我美梦成真
and being on the Justice League is a dream come true.
但只是，我感觉...
It's just-- I feel like I'm not--
你「感觉」，就是问题所在
You feel. That's the problem.
你应该将自己的情绪隐藏起来
You need to stuff your emotions deep down inside.
什么也不要感觉
Feel nothing.
只需要针对这个充满懦弱迷信罪犯的世界做出计划，然后行动
Only plot, plan and react to a world
full of cowardly, superstitious criminals.
这才是健康的生活方式
It's the healthy thing to do.
但是我总觉得我跟不上进度
But I feel like I'm just not up to speed.
嗯，我在队伍里可能显得有些不平衡
well，Having me on the team kinds of throws off the average.
但如果你真想跟上节奏
But if you really wanna up your game...
你只需要在不稳定的化学物品包围的时候 然后被雷劈一劈
All you have to do is getting hit by lightning when surrounded by chemicals and...
你干这行很轻松啊
You make it seem so easy.
你知道以前在飞行学校的时候我们说什么吗？
You know what we used to say in flight school?
直到你成功之前，一定要假装你已经成功了
Fake it till you make it.
你只需要探求内心，男人起来...
You just gotta dig deep and man up...
或者机器起来...
or machine up...
或者管他的
or whatever.
看起来无论我做什么都是错的
Seems like whatever I do, it's the wrong call.
你是不是有些小小的忧郁，钢骨?
Are you feeling a teensy bit blue, Cyborg?
给你唱首我们堪萨斯人经常唱的歌吧，非常振奋人心
Here's a little song we used to sing
back in Kansas. Always cheered me up.
噢 一个农夫需要把子 梨和锄头
Oh, a farmer needs a rake
And a plow and a hoe
他还必须精力旺盛 懂得尝试
And lots of pep and some zip
And a tiny pinch of go
穿着他的吊带裤 帽子和鞋子
And get into his overalls
And hat and shoes
如果他一开始就放弃 那早晨工作注定不顺利
If he wants to lose
The early morning blues
哈哈
Ha-ha.
然后超人给我唱了首我完全听不懂的歌
And then Superman sang me a song that I did not get at all.
哦，对，我以前也听过那首歌
Oh, yes, I've heard that song before.
我也完全没懂
I didn't get it either.
听着，维克，你回顾最近几场战斗，发现了很多不足
Listen, Vic, you look at your recent battles
and see mistakes.
那是你的看法
That's just your perception...
而不是别人的看法
not necessarily the perception of others...
更不是我对你的看法
and certainly not my perception of you.
你是个年轻的英雄，前途光明
You're a young hero
with a lot going for you.
你只需要相信自己的直觉
You just have to trust your instincts.
给自己时间成长并相信自己
Give yourself time to grow and believe in yourself.
所以你是说我应该强化我的机械部件，
So you're saying I should really beef up my cybernetic components
然后我就会更加自信
so I can then trust myself.
正确...等等，什么？不是
Exact-- Wait, what? No.
谢谢，神奇女侠，这就是我将要做的
Thanks, Wonder Woman. That's exactly what I'll do.
现在就开始
Right now.
真不知道我以前怎么没想到，只需要升级装备就好啦
I don't know why I didn't think of it before.Just gotta gear up.
Booyah.
你好啊，蝙蝠侠
What's up, Batman?
Mm.
你过得怎样，哈尔？
How you feeling, Hal?
我活在美梦里，维克，而且我的方式比闪电侠更好
I'm living the dream, Vic.
And I'm doing it way better than Flash.
-蝙蝠侠 -祝你今天愉快
- Batman. -Have a nice day.
蝙蝠侠，我知道这听起来很奇怪...
Batman, I know this must sound strange...
但是我觉得我刚刚经过你两次...而且我...
but I think I just passed you twice, and I don't...
也许如果你专注于超级英雄的责任
Perhaps if you concentrated on superheroing
而不是到处管多管闲事
instead of butting into
other people's business
你才会成为一个更好的正义联盟成员
you'd be a better Justice League member.
额...好吧，对不起
Oh, right. Sorry.
这就是我学到的方式，
And that's how I learned
千万不要在谷仓里关着灯去给奶牛挤奶
you should never milk a cow in the barn when the lights are off.
嘿，等一下
Hey, wait up.
嘿，蝙蝠侠，刚刚我遇到你的时候
Hey, Batman, maybe that was meant...
也许你可以给点更善意一点的批评...
to be more constructive criticism when I passed you just now--
我遇见你时什么都没说啊
I didn't say anything when you walked by just now.
不，你说了，还叫我别多管闲事
Yes, you did. And you told me to butt out.
这有点无礼
Came off a little rude.
蝙蝠侠永远不会跟你说叫你别多管闲事
Batman would never tell you to put your butt out.
他也许是黑暗骑士，但是对我来说，他是个文雅的巡警
He may be the Dark Knight,
but to me, he's the Polite Patrolman.
但那不是官方暱称，我自己想出来的
But that's not an official nickname. I came up with it myself.
你的机械眼里一定有双重影像了，让我来帮你
You must be getting a double image in your cybernetic eye. Let me help.
好点了吗？
There. Better?
我们晚一点再继续讨论吧
We'll have to table this little chat until later.
那个核反应堆出事了，这个是政府
It's that nuketron reactor that went online,
the one the government hopes...
能够解决世界能源问题的的希望
will provide a solution to the world's energy needs.
希波吕忒的发网，核反应堆出故障了
By Hippolyta's hairnet, the reactor is malfunctioning.
它快要核心融解了
It's in danger of a total meltdown.
核心融解会威胁到成千上万居民的安全
A core meltdown would endanger thousands of citizens.
-你的命令是什么，蝙蝠侠 - 出发
- What are your orders, Batman?
-Let's go.
它在那爆着呢
There she blows.
懂吗，因为它快爆炸了
Get it? Because it's gonna blow up.
现在不是说笑话的时候，绿灯侠，钢骨，能源核心还有多久融解
Not now, Green Lantern. Cyborg, how long
before the energy core melts down?
真奇怪，我的指示器显示一切正常
This is strange. My readouts don't detect anything wrong.
一切看起来很正常
Everything looks normal.
该去加点机油了吧，铁皮人，你自己看看那东西
Time for an oil change, Tin Man? Look at that thing.
那就跟蝙蝠侠笑一样「正常」
That's about as normal
as Batman smiling.
你的指示是什么，无畏的领袖？
What are your orders, fearless leader?
钢骨和我警戒边线
Cyborg and I will secure the perimeter.
闪电侠，你和神奇女侠把工作人员从里面救出来
Flash, you and Wonder Woman
get the power plant crew out of that inferno.
超人和哈尔，你们对核辐射免疫，
Superman and Hal,
you're both immune to radiation.
去阻止能源核心融解
Stop the energy core from melting down...
要不然大都会接下来一万年都将是个荒无人烟的核辐射地带
or else Metropolis becomes a lifeless radiation hot zone for the next 10,000 years.
额...这算是鼓舞士气的话?
Ugh. That's a pep talk?
记得提醒我永远不要参加你的励志讲座
Remind me to never attend your motivational seminars.
上吧，伙计们
Let's do this, guys.
别担心，伙计们，我分分钟把你们救出去
Don't worry, fellas, I'll have you out of danger in a flash.
Ooh.
Huh?
卡桑德拉的胸衣，你们没看见你们处于危险之中吗？
Cassandra's corset, can't you see the danger you're in?
Huh?
嘿，我的三明治
Hey, my sandwich.
蝙蝠侠，我的读数还是一切正常
Batman,I'm still reading everything is normal.
你的软件问题我们回去再解决
We'll deal with your software glitches when we get back.
超人，哈尔，你们看见了什么?
Superman, Hal, what do you see?
供水系统和反应堆之间的冷却液泵已经毁了
The coolant pump between the water supply and reactor core is toast.
难怪过热了，我来解决
No wonder it's overheating. I'm on it.
来自核反应堆内部的报道
Reporting from inside the nuketron reactor.
看来核反应堆随时都会爆炸
It looks as though this reactor will blow at any moment.
造成史上最大的人为灾祸
Making this the greatest man-made catastrophe of all time.
我这该能得普利策奖了吧
I'd better get a Pulitzer for this.
是露易斯，她在核反应堆里
It's Lois. She's in the reactor.
超人，救命
Superman, help!
坚持住，露易斯
There you go, Lois.
我马上把你救出去...
Now let's get you out of here before--
露易斯？
Lois?
哈尔
Hal.
你的冷却液泵不起作用
Your coolant pump isn't working.
那你来压啊
Then you come pump it.
蝙蝠侠，核心里的温度比太阳还高
Batman, the core temperature is hotter than the sun.
核心快要全面熔毁了，我们只有几分钟时间
We're in full meltdown. We have only about a minute
来阻止核心把大都会夷为平地了
to stop the core from burning and irradiating Metropolis.
-我的感应器依旧... -把核心控制到安全温度，
- My sensors aren't--
-Cool the core to a safer temperature...
一直撑到把它搬出大楼
long enough to get it out of the building.
我尽量
I'll do my best.
哈尔，去帮超人把核心搬出去
Hal, help Superman get that core out of there.
已经开始了，蝙蝠
Already on it, Bats.
有些不对劲啊
someting's not right here.
抓稳了
Hold steady.
准备
Get ready.
走你
Here we go.
拯救世界
Saved the day.
又一次
Again.
嘿，你懂我了，哈哈哈
Hey, you got it. Ha-ha-ha.
一号摄像机
Camera one.
二号摄像机
Camera two.
一号摄像机
Camera one.
二号摄像机
Camera two.
钢骨呼叫蝙蝠侠，发现些有些奇怪的情况
Cyborg to Batman, something's funny here.
我是说「出事了」的意思，不是「哈哈哈」的意思
And I mean funny "messed up," not funny "ha-ha-ha."
看来反应堆根本没出问题
There was never anything wrong with the reactor.
我开始觉得你是对的了
I'm beginning to think you're right.
核反应堆完全毁了
Aw, the nuketron reactor is finished.
你们为什么要毁掉我们的能源站
Why did you destroy our power plant?
你们怎么了，瞎吗？——咳咳
- What are you, blind? -Ahem.
我的同事是想说，你们可能没注意到...
What my colleague means to say is that you may not have noticed...
你们的新能源站刚刚险些熔毁？
...your new power plant was experiencing a meltdown?
你看，现在看起来确实不像有熔毁的情况发生
You know, now it does look a little less melty.
唯一的损坏是我们自己造成的
The only damage is the damage we inflicted ourselves.
超人，你和你的联盟刚刚毁掉了价值数十亿的能源设施...
Superman，You and the league have just destroyed
a multibillion-dollar power plant...
而这本来可以使大都会在能源供应问题上领先世界
that could've made Metropolis a world leader in energy production.
-你们还有什么可说的 -露易斯，你没事
- What do you have to say for yourselves?
-Lois, you're okay.
没事？我气坏了，大家也一样，你对那些说正义联盟
Okay? I'm livid, like everyone else on Earth.
What do you say to your critics...
权力太大的批评家有什么想说的
who claim the Justice League has too much power and no oversight?
-哇哦哇哦，什么批评家 -我爸爸就是一个
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. What critics?
-My daddy, for one.
-他是你爸爸？ -谁是你爸爸？
- He's your daddy?
- Who's your daddy?
我知道他是你爸爸
I knew he was your daddy.
根本没有什么什么融解，反应堆工作正常
There was no meltdown. The reactor was working fine.
你们看见了吗，
Do you see, people?
我们让这群超能团队无拘无束
We let super-powered goons run around unrestricted...
而这就是必然发生的结果
and this is the type of thing that is bound to happen.
我是说，看看那个机器人的武器
I mean, just look at all the weapons on the robot one.
他们随时可能擦枪走火
They could go off at any moment.
武器是邪恶的
- Boo! - Weapons are evil!
我讨厌枪
I don't like guns!
所谓的正义联盟需要为他们的罪行付出代价
The so-called Justice League needs to pay for its crimes.
在发生更糟糕的情况之前他们必须受到控制
They must be controlled before something worse takes place.
我们中计了，
We've been had.
根本没有核心融解
There was no meltdown.
大家大家，不要慌乱
People, people, don't panic.
这肯定有什么天大的误会
This has apparently been one big misunderstanding.
我忍不住插嘴了 希望你不要介意
I just jumped in there. I hope you don't mind.
人们比较喜欢你 就由你来说吧
You're the people person. I'll let you run with this.
正义联盟是负责任的
The Justice League is all about responsibility.
我确信一旦我们把一切解释清楚...
I'm sure that once we've explained everything...
世界法庭会很乐意的宣告我们...
the world court will happily find us--
-罪名成立 -啥？！
- Guilty as charged. -What?
在大都会投放臭气弹，
For the charges of stink bombing Metropolis...
进攻绝密的政府设施，
attacking a top secret government facility...
还有荒唐的破坏，差点造成核炉心熔毁
and wanton destruction nearly causing a nuclear meltdown...
正义联盟将被驱逐出地球
the Justice League is banished from the planet Earth.
立即生效
Effective immediately.
正义联盟垮台
Down with the Justice League!
我以前喜欢他们，现在不了
I used to like them, but now I don't.
叫这个蓝大个替我们说话真是好主意啊
Nice call letting the big blue Boy Scout speak for us.
这就是为啥我投票给神奇女侠
And that's why I voted for Wonder Woman.
好了，这个阴谋到此为止了
All right, this conspiracy has gone far enough.
我们必须弄个水落石出，我们藏入黑暗，低调行动
We have to get to the bottom of it.
We're going dark. Off the grid.
我们在阴影中解决这个谜团，准备好跟随我的领导然后
We'll work from the shadows to solve this mystery. Get ready to follow my lead and--
-不 -你在干什么?
- Nope. -What are you doing?
我是正义联盟的领导
I'm the leader of the Justice League.
是你坚持要选我做领导的
You've made a point of following my orders.
这次不行，组建正义联盟就是为了为世界人民服务
Not this time. The Justice League was
formed to serve the people of the world.
他们否决了你的权力，蝙蝠侠
They overrule your authority, Batman.
如果他们想要我们走，我们就走
If they want us gone, we go.
说得好，外星人
Nice speech, alien.
警卫，把这些英雄赶出我的视线
Guards, get these heroes out of my sight.
就这样世界告别了正义联盟，总算摆脱了他们
And so the world says goodbye and good riddance to the Justice League.
太好了
Yes. All right.
来击掌
High five. Heh.
现在擦掉眼泪，钢骨，银河可是很大的
Now, wipe away those tears, Cyborg. It's a big galaxy.
跟着我让我们尽情狂欢
Stick with me and we'll have a blast.
你知道吗，我知道一颗有坏掉的烤面包机居住的星球
You know, I know a planet inhabited by broken toasters.
说不定我们还可以给你找个女朋友
Maybe we can find you a girlfriend.
我觉得你可以放开蝙蝠侠了 ——嗯?
- I think you can let go of Batman now. -Hmm?
哦，对不起啊，蝙蝠侠
Oh. Heh. Sorry about that, Batman.
但是法律就是法律
But the law is the law.
我们等会再来谈谈你的小叛乱
We'll discuss your little mutiny later.
Our job now is to gather evidence...
现在我们的任务是搜集证据证明我们是被陷害的，然后重返地球
prove we were framed and then return to Earth.
恐怕重返地球是不可能了
I'm afraid returning to Earth is not an option.
塞尼斯托，我速速去把他搞定了
Sinestro. I'll make quick work of him.
你这叫快？要是我早就结束了
You call this quick? I'd be totally done by now.
对吧
Right?
我只是来给你们个小小的离别礼物
I just came to give you a little farewell gift.
希望你还留着礼物的发票，塞尼斯托
I hope you kept the gift receipt, Sinestro.
保持射击，他必须得维持那面护盾就没法攻击我们了
Keep firing. He'll have to keep up that shield and won't be able to attack.
想当然
Think so?
来见见我的新朋友
Meet my new best friend.
他被称为父盒
It's called a Father Box.
这不会让你们大吃一惊吗？
Doesn't this just bowl you over?
准备被冲到银河系另一头吧
Prepare to be flushed to the other side of the galaxy.
我懂啦，冲...
Oh, I get it. Bowl. Flush.
就像冲厕所一样
Like a toilet!
然后我说：
And then I said:
「准备被冲到银河系另一头吧」
"Prepare to be flushed to the other side of the galaxy."
我打赌闪电侠肯定没听懂
I bet Flash didn't get it.
恭喜我们
Congratulations to us all.
毁灭军团胜利了
The Legion of Doom is victorious.
胜利者的奖励是...
And to the victors go the spoils.
地球是我们的啦
- The Earth is ours.
- Yeah!
Yes!
就像之前讨论的那样，我们要瓜分战利品
As discussed earlier, we will be dividing up the loot.
战利品当然指的是地球上所有的东西
In this case, that means everything on Earth.
我要所有黄色的东西
I claim everything yellow.
没门，香蕉是黄色的
No way. Bananas are yellow.
这个，你可以要绿香蕉嘛
Well, you can have the green bananas.
黄金不也是黄的吗，这不公平你知道吧
Is gold yellow? Because, you know, that's not fair.
你不能直接要所有黄色的东西
You can't just call all yellow.
那我要红色，世上所有红色的东西都是我的
I call red. Everything red is mine.
红宝石，唇膏，苹果
Rubies, lipstick, apples.
大海是蓝色的
The ocean's blue.
塞尼斯托 - 海里所有的东西都是我的 - 作为冲走正义联盟的奖励
Sinestro - Everything in the ocean is mine.
as a bonus for flushing the Justice League
为什么不给自己一些奖励
why don't you treat yourself?
去摧毁正义大厅，这样当征服开始时
Go destroy their Hall of Justice,
so when the conquest begins...
人们就会知道他们已经无人可以求助了
people will know they have no one to turn to.
哈哈，不介意的话我就去做了
Heh-heh. Don't mind if I do.
莱克斯，所有关于这些征服
Lex, all this talk of conquest...
像战利品一样瓜分世界的这些对话
...of dividing this planet like the spoils of war...
我们难道不是带来自由的解放者吗
are we not liberators bringing freedom?
是啊，是啊，当然，尚恩，我们正在解放他们
Yes. Yes. Of course, J'onn. We are freeing them.
我们让他们从自由做决定中解放出来
We're freeing them of making their own decisions.
不要用你那能心灵感应的绿脑袋担心了，相信我
Don't you worry your telepathic green head about it. Trust me.
我会的
I Will.
暂时
For now.
火星人有什么问题吗
Problems with the Martian?
他快发现了
He's catching on.
不过幸运的是，他已经失去利用价值了
Fortunately, he's already served his purpose.
什么时候有空就把他干掉
Feel free to eliminate him permanently.
哦，披萨到了
Oh, the pizza's here.
我们快被吸进黑洞了，抓紧
We're caught in the gravity pull of that black hole. Hang tight.
抓着呢
Hanging.
加油，宝贝，你能行的
Come on, baby. You got this.
呃，我已经把我所有意念都给了她，但是我还是逃不开引力
Ugh. I'm giving her all the willpower I've got,
but I just can't escape its gravity.
-你们在后面还好吗? - 还好
- You guys all right back there? - All right.
嗷
Ow.
哦，可怜的朋友
Oh, poor friend.
我应该给你唱一首歌颂阵亡英雄的弥斯库拉之歌给你
I shall sing the Themysciran song of dead heroes for you.
不用唱歌，神奇女侠
No need to sing, Wonder Woman.
他是个假人
He's just a dummy.
那又怎样，他是我们的朋友
That doesn't matter. He was our friend.
不，那是电子机器人
No, that was Cy-bot. Huh.
难怪我们起飞后他就表现的怪怪的
No wonder he was acting weird ever since takeoff.
那么两个问题来了
Which leaves us with two questions:
我们怎么逃离这里
How do we get out of this jam
还有真正的钢骨在哪里
and where is the real Cyborg?
我不想就这么抛下伙计们的
I hate to leave the guys in a lurch...
但是我知道事有些不对劲
...but I know there was something fishy going on.
这肯定有什么线索，但是在哪呢
There must be some clue here, but where?
在哪？在哪？
Where? Where?
哈，一条线索
Ah! A clue.
某种奇怪的外星科技
Some kind of weird alien tech.
这怎么会在这？最好看看监控录像
How'd this get here? Better check the security tapes.
Huh?
噢，我记得你
Oh, I know you.
啊哈，那就是我在人群中看到的
Aha! That's the thing I saw.
我就知道它不可能是随便一个穿着红内裤的绿色家伙
I knew it couldn't have been some random green guy in red underwear.
现在需要我做的就是带着证据离开并且证明正义联盟的清白
All I have to do is get this evidence out there and clear the Justice League.
向谁去证明？
Clear them with who?
还有几个小时，毁灭军团就会统治世界了
Within a few hours, the Legion of Doom will have taken over the world.
我真是伤心
How sad for me.
正义联盟剩下的唯一成员...
Only one member of the Justice League left...
是最弱的一个
and it's the weakest one.
我觉得你已经知道结局了对吧，半人类
I think you already know how this ends,
don't you, half-man?
你没打中
You missed.
得赶快走，这证据比我去报仇重要多了
Gotta keep moving. This evidence is more important than me getting payback.
Whoa!
嘿，那是神奇女侠的隐形飞机
Hey, that was Wonder Woman's Invisible Jet.
哦，当她发现你干了什么好事，你就有大麻烦了
Oh, when she finds out what you did,
you are gonna be in so much trouble.
她永远也不会发现
She'll never find out...
正义联盟剩下的人也是
nor will the rest of the Justice League...
因为我把他们冲到宇宙对面去了
because I flushed them all to the opposite side of the universe.
我说是「冲」，因为我弄了个虫洞知道吗
I say flushed because I created this Wormhole, you see...
然后它相当于...
and it resembled a--
你当时要是在就好啦
You just had to be there.
尽管逃吧，
Go ahead, run.
这只会让你最终的失败更令人愉悦
It'll make your final defeat all the more enjoyable.
要活着，要找到办法阻止军团
Gotta stay alive. Gotta find a way to stop the legion.
什么，正义联盟？
What? The Justice League?
还活着？
Alive?
哈？他说什么
What? What's he talking about?
不可能
Impossible.
不是不可能
Not impossible.
对我来说
- For me. -Ah!
你已经被我精神控制了，塞尼斯托
You are under my mental control,Sinestro.
唯一自由的方式就是照我说的做
The only way to be set free is to do what I ask.
你就是那个陷害我们的变形人，对吧，你对他做了什么
You're the shape-shifter who set us up,
aren't you? What'd you do to him?
像我这样的火星人，拥有影响心智的能力
Martians, like me, have the ability to influence minds.
有机物的心智
Organic minds.
但你不一样，钢骨
Unlike yours, Cyborg.
哦，能源站，
Oh, the power plant.
其他人都看见能源站出故障了
Everyone else saw the plant malfunctioning...
是因为你让他们看见的
because you were making them see that.
但是我的电子有机大脑对你的能力免疫
But my cyber-organic brain is immune to your powers.
我还是不相信你
I still don't trust you.
请停下
Please. Stop.
我是来帮忙的
I am here to help.
就像你「帮忙」让正义联盟被驱逐
Pfft. Like you helped the Justice League get banished?
现在整个世界已经是毁灭军团唾手可得的自助餐了
The world is an all-you-can-conquer buffet for the Legion of Doom.
我被骗了
I was tricked.
莱克斯·卢瑟把我从52区放了出来
Lex Luthor freed me from Area 52.
我以为他是个解放者
I thought he was a liberator.
我的判断力被复仇的阴云所蒙蔽
I let my thirst for vengeance cloud my judgment.
拜托你，让我来纠正所犯下的错误
Please, let me make this right.
我想帮助你
I want to help you.
-怎么帮 -我有一些想法
- How? -I have some thoughts.
最后，瓦努阿图，越南，委内瑞拉，维京群岛
Finally. Vanuatu, Vietnam, Venezuela, Virgin Islands...
也门，赞比亚还有津巴布韦是寒冷队长的
Yemen, Zambia and Zimbabwe will go to Captain Cold.
等等，什么，为什么我得到的是字母表最后面的
Wait, what? Why do I have to get the end of the alphabet?
格鲁德，你这迂腐的灵长类动物，你让整个军团都无聊得睡着了
Grodd, you pedantic primate.
You've bored the Legion of Doom to sleep.
够了
Enough of this.
征服地球，开始
Let the conquest of the Earth begin.
-哇哦，看看这些 -不错的科技
- Wow, look at all of this.
-lmpressive technology.
好了，塞尼斯托，该把正义联盟冲回来了
All right, Sinestro, time to un-flush the Justice League.
哈哈哈，冲，我喜欢这个
Heh-heh-heh. Flush. That's a good one.
起作用了，继续加油
Unh. It's working. Keep pouring it on.
标枪号可是采用了最先进技术的飞行器，
The Javelin is a state-of-the-art spacecraft.
从没想过有一天我们得到外面推它
Never thought we'd have to get out and push.
雅典娜倒塌的拱门的，我们回家的路
Athena's fallen arches, our way home.
大家一起推啊
Everyone, heave.
Yeah!
Mm.
你召唤我
You summoned me?
毫无疑问是想好好称赞一下
No doubt to heap praise upon my brilliant execution...
我绝妙的计划毁掉了正义联盟吧
of our plan to end the Justice League?
不要忘了你的地位，人类
Remember your place, human.
你还没完成你的任务
You haven't completed your end of the agreement yet.
为了确保我们的胜利，我带了几个新礼物
To ensure our victory, I have provided a few more gifts.
Huh?
谁会想到莱克斯会藏有机器猴呢
Who knew Lex had robo-monkeys up his sleeve?
好好表现一下吧
Color me impressed.
前进，我的军团
Forward, my legions.
这城市很快就是我们的了
The city will soon be ours.
大都会的下场也就是整个世界的下场
And as goes Metropolis, so goes the world.
统治世界就是好，
We lead the world and there's no doubt
没有事就玩和闹
When there's no work We play and shout
你们好，前任世界统治者
Hello, former rulers of the world.
我是莱克斯·卢瑟
It's Lex Luthor.
是卢梭还是卢瑟
Is it Luther or Luthor?
我，莱克斯·卢瑟，本世代最伟大的罪犯，
I, Lex Luthor,the greatest criminal mind of our time...
毁灭军团的统治者
and the leaderof the nefarious Legion of Doom...
要求世界政府立即投降
declare the immediate surrender of the world's governments.
如果你们拒绝
If you refuse...
那大都会就是你们的下场
well, let's just say Metropolis is about to be a cautionary tale.
好，计划是这样的
Okay, here's the plan.
哈尔，你，闪电侠和神奇女侠拿下毁灭大厅
Hal, you, Flash and Wonder Woman take out the Hall of Doom.
超人和我会阻止格鲁德的地面军队
Superman and I will stop Grodd and the forces on the ground.
-那我干什么 -我需要你待在这里，钢骨
- What about me?
-I need you to stay in the hall, Cyborg.
守住这里，同时盯着这个火星人
Hold down the fort. And also keep an eye on this Martian.
我告诉过你，蝙蝠侠，我不是一个威胁
I told you, Batman, I am not a threat.
你当然这么说
So you say.
但是你确实伪装我们，陷害我们，让我们被驱逐出地球
But you did impersonate us, frame us,
and cause our banishment from Earth.
是的，但除了这些
Yes, but other than that...
蝙蝠侠，我想跟你一起去
Batman, I wanna go with you.
钢骨，你单独战斗，就像我原本想做的
Cyborg, by going rogue,like I wanted to...
你救了我们大家
you saved us all.
但是现在，我需要你确保塞尼斯托和火星人呆在这
But right now, I need you to make sure
Sinestro and the Martian stay put.
你能做到吗，士兵？
Can you do that, soldier?
遵命，长官
Yes, sir.
胜利是我们的
Victory is ours!
-不尽然 -什么
- Not quite. - What?
别担心，格鲁德
Don't worry, Grodd.
你可以在黑门监狱吃香蕉吃个够
You can have all the bananas you want in Blackgate Prison.
干掉他
Destroy him.
哈哈，你们绝对不会想到我设计了这个蝙蝠-猩猩战斗装甲
Ha-ha. Little did you suspect that I designed the Bat-gorilla battle suit...
就是为了这种时候准备的
for just such an occasion.
Ah. Ha-ha-ha.
背后偷袭
Shooting a man in the back?
我以为你不会这么低级，格鲁德
I thought you were more evolved than that,Grodd.
Huh?
卢瑟，我们有伴了
Luthor, we have company.
啊，正义联盟，我以为我们干掉他们了
Ah! The Justice League.I thought we ended them.
为什么他们就不能别回来呢
Why won't they just stay ended?
让我给你表演一下该怎么做
Let me show you how it's done.
那我得脑袋后面长眼睛才行
I'd have to have eyes in the back of my head...
因为我会领先你一大截
since I'll be way ahead of you.
我打算叫这个网胜
I'll consider this a net victory.
享受冷板凳时光吧，闪电侠
Enjoy your time on the bench, Flash.
看看真正的玩家怎么得分
Watch a real player score some points.
所以你喜欢玩游戏，哈?
So you like to play games, huh?
游戏开始
Game on.
15，30，40
Fifteen. Thirty. Forty.
我今天热血沸腾
I'm on fire today.
那我给你来个冰袋冷静冷静
Let me cool you off with an ice pack.
哈？啊！
Huh? Aah!
嘿嘿，看来你该先热热身的，0分
Heh-heh. Looks like you should've warmed up. Zero points.
闪电侠逃脱，10分
Flash escaping，Ten points.
不不不，我得了40
No, no, no, I had 40.
加上从冰里逃出来，还有额外的15分
Plus escape from ice,so that's an extra 15.
给你一个惊喜，神奇女侠
I've got a little surprise for you, Wonder Woman.
那不算什么，这才是惊喜
Uh, that wasn't the surprise.This is the surprise.
我们惊喜用完了，怎么阻止她
We're out of surprises.How do we stop her?
只需利用她的一个缺点：她的同情心
By exploiting her one weakness: her compassion.
没打中，卢瑟
You missed, Lex.
是吗
Did I?
不，动物医院
No. The animal hospital.
哦，我们该逃了
Oh, we should run.
我也想啊，但我吓得动不了了
I would, but I'm frozen with fear.
500分
Five hundred points.
600分
Six hundred points.
你比一桶猴子还无趣
You're less fun than a barrel of monkeys.
到底还有多少，还...
How many of these are there, any...
不，氪石
No. Kryptonite.
坚持住，超人，我来了
Hold on, Superman. I'm coming.
毁灭大厅是专门设计出来
The Hall of Doom was specifically designed...
利用你们的弱点和抵御你们的能力
to withstand your powers and exploit your weaknesses.
打败整个正义联盟只是个时间问题
It is only a matter of time before it defeats the entire Justice League.
不是整个联盟，我的绿色朋友，我有个主意
Not the entire league, my green friend.I have an idea.
正义大厅怎么了
What's happening to the Hall of Justice?
我给它升级了，这是我的兴趣爱好
I gave it an upgrade. It's my hobby.
3，2，1
Three, two, one.
站稳了
Hold on.
Yoo-hoo!
有人在吗
anybody home?
什么？快把这个关了
What? Stop this transmission.
它从哪冒出来的
Where is it coming from?
卢瑟，侦测到一个大家伙朝我们飞来
Luthor, I'm picking up something big flying towards us.
大屏幕
On the screen.
不，这不可能
No. It can't be.
快看，是鸟
Look, it's a giant bird.
不，是飞机
No, it's a plane.
额，反正肯定不是超人
Well, it certainly isn't Superman.
他看上去在打盹
He seems to be taking a nap.
我也想打个盹
I could use a nap.
钢骨
Cyborg.
现在让他们看看我们的本事
Now let's show them what we got.
而且我们很有范儿
And we got style.
发射迪斯科导弹
Launch disco missiles.
快放开我们正式选举的领袖，格鲁德
Unhand our duly elected leader, Grodd.
哈?
Huh?
很高兴在我有难时有你做我的坚强后盾，超人
Good to know you have my back when it counts, Superman.
看来是钢骨是我们所有人的后盾
Looks like Cyborg had all our backs.
有朝一日，他会成为一个伟大的领袖
He'll make a great leader someday.
上吧
Let's go.
能射什么就赶快射出去，开火
Shoot everything we've got at them. Fire.
星星护盾，开启
Star shield, activate.
我把这个称为糊你熊脸终结技
I call this my in-your-face finale.
Booyah! Booyah!
走了
Come on.
我先到宠物医院的，900分
I got to the pet hospital first.Nine hundred points.
哇哦，神奇女侠，这看起来挺重的
Wow, Wonder Woman,that looks pretty heavy.
对你来说
Even for you.
用你的热视线焊接大楼的裂缝
Use your heat vision to seal the cracks in the building.
好主意
Great idea.
别担心，鸟儿们都安全了
Don't worry, the birds are safe.
那算1000分
That's a thousand points.
鸟？哈，我救的可是猫
Birds? Ha! I've saved cats.
这可值5000分
That's 5000 points.
你在逗我吗？狗，我救了狗
Are you kidding me? Dogs. I've saved dogs.
一百万分
One million points.
这荒唐的我比你强的游戏简直够了
This ridiculous one-upsmanship has gone on long enough.
我们帮助别人，是因为这是正确的事
We help people because it's the right thing to do.
真正的英雄从不计分
True heroes do not keep score.
呃，她是对的，你知道的 - 是啊
Ugh. She's right, you know. - Yeah.
但是现在不计分我的本事也比你强
But I'm totally better at not keeping score than you.
不可能
Nuh-uh.
哦，不，想都别想
Oh, no, you don't.
你们别想逃
You aren't going anywhere.
拜托，请交给我
Please, leave this to me.
Yipe!
太酷了
That was so cool.
看来你总是能拿下敌人
Looks like you always get your man.
就像...火星猎人一样
Like you're some kind of Martian manhunter.
嗯，这名字不错
Hmm. I like it.
最后一个猎物
One last hunt.
但，但，但是我解放了你
But-- But-- But I freed you.
如果不是我，你现在还被关着呢
If it wasn't for me,you'd still be held prisoner.
这一点我的确很感激
For that, I am grateful.
所以你会放我走
So you'll let me go?
是的，但我不保证他们也会
Yes, but I'm afraid they may not.
耶，正义联盟
Yay, Justice League!
- 驱逐你们不好意思啊，是我们的错 -太好了
- Sorry we exiled you guys. Our bad.- All right!
好，就这样了
Well, that's that.
我想毁灭军团很长一段时间都不能兴风作浪了
Guess it'll be quite a while before
the Legion of Doom can make any trouble.
对，说的不错
Yes, that's true.
多亏了你，钢骨
Thanks to you, Cyborg.
我们都活了下来，地球也脱离了危险
We're all alive,and the Earth is out of danger...
因为你相信了自己的直觉
because you trusted your instincts.
干得不错
Good job.
至于你，我为这颗星球对待你的方式感到十分抱歉
As for you, I couldn't be more sorry for the way
this planet treated you when you arrived.
但有时我们对还没有见过的事物保持怀疑
But sometimes we're a bit suspicious of things we haven't seen before.
我们无畏的领袖曾经也是这么对我的
Our fearless leader used to think the same of me.
请理解，这毕竟是少数人
Please know that was just one narrow individual.
地球人是很热情的
The people of Earth can be very welcoming.
根据联盟规定，我还能当37秒钟的领导
According to the bylaws of the league,
I'm only leader for another 37 seconds.
然后又会重新选举
Then it'll be time for another election.
我还是会投你，蝙蝠
You've still got my vote, Bats.
我作为领导的最后一个决定，是为我们的新同伴提供
My final act as leader is to offer a Justice League membership...
一个正义联盟的席位
to our new ally.
真的吗，那这样的话，欢迎加入
Really? Well, in that case,welcome to the team.
看来我不仅有了新的星球
It appears I not only have a new planet.
还有了一个新的家庭
but a new family.
Yeah!
派对，走起
Let's party!
别着急
Not so fast.
你们要为这一系列损害负责
I'm holding you all personally responsible for this damage.
火星猎人
Manhunter.
如果你们不...
And if you don't--
电子机器人，为派对而生
Cy-bot lives to party.
很好，摇摆起来
All right. Boogie.
Hmm.
通话，达克赛德
Come in, Darkseid.
莱克斯·卢瑟呼叫达克赛德
This is Lex Luthor to Darkseid.
我能听见，人类
Darkseid hears you, human.
时候到了
It's about time.
我想逃出去
I want out of here.
你当然想，卢瑟
Of course you do, Luthor.
但和我有什么关系
What is that to me?
我给了你要的所有工具，还不止
I gave you the tools you needed
and more.
你还是失败了
Still you failed.
达克赛德，你必须得帮我
Darkseid, you must help me.
不，我不需要为你做任何事
No. I need do nothing for you.
但如果我想要地球
But if I want the Earth...
那可恶的正义联盟，必须被毁灭
and the accursed Justice League destroyed...
然后我将找到同盟
then I must reach across the aisle.
敌人的敌人就是我的朋友
For the enemy of my enemy is my friend.